Contact

https://django-portfolioresume.onrender.com

7475 Litabe street Orlando West

thamsanqambodla@gmail. com

+27 81 524 4505

Skills

Python Developer Backend

django

RESTAPI's

DRF

CI/CD Git & Github

HTML5 & CSS

Azure Cloud

Javascript

Postgres

Languages

Engl i sh

Thamsanqa Mbodla

PYTHON DEVELOPER

About me

Analytical , motivated and hard working Python Developer with over 3 years of experience designing, debugging and troubleshooting applications using Django and Python programming language. Hoping to use my advanced developerment skill to build and enhance banking application.

Experience

Python Developer Backend

Grace Bible Church 2020 - present

system development, designing, implementing and managing software programs, testing and evaluating new programs, identifying areas for modification in existing programs.

Python application developer

Kgafa Tech

2021 - present

system development, subsequently developing creating developing new applications, writing and implementing efficient code, designing and managing software programs

github account

https://github.com/Thamsanqa-git

Education

(2022-2023) Python Intermediate

Solo learn

functional programming and OOP concepts,system development and management

(2022) Programming with Python

Simplilearn

The professional of deepening my skills and advancing career choice

(2020) Coding Intro

IBM

Computer engineering course , python intro data structures and algorithms